Austin Schroeder

(515) 490-8804 || <u>austinsoundy@gmail.com</u> || <u>LinkedIn</u> || <u>Github</u> || <u>Portfolio</u> San Diego, CA

Objective

I'm a Software Developer and excited to find my next role at a company where I can build great products and continue to master the craft. A long time ago, in a galaxy far far away... I organized multiple aspects of large scale live concerts, tours, and events - specializing in audio engineering. I rock at coordinating logistics, creating efficiency, team building, and working in a fast-paced environment with tight deadlines.

Technical Skills

JavaScript, React, jQuery, HTML, CSS, Express, Node.js, MongoDB, Python, Django, PostgreSQL, Bootstrap, Firebase

Projects

- JavaScript Racer Fun JavaScript based game with a racing tortoise and hare HTML, CSS, JS, jQuery
- CageDB Full CRUD web app showcasing Nicolas Cage movies Python, Django, HTML, CSS-Materialize
- **Melty** Full CRUD website for customers interested in finding plant based cheeses in their area HTML, MongoDB, Mongoose, NodeJS, ExpressJS

Experience

Live Concert Production-Independent Contractor: 2011 - 2021

Positions include:

- Production Manager: Pre-planned and executed all technical logistics for individual events, as well as
 entire tours. Working with six-figure budgets on securing production vendors and maintaining
 relationships. Hiring/firing crew members. Manage conflicting priorities. Acts include: <u>Tom Morello</u>
 <u>Projects, Cypress Hill, Rachel Platten, Iggy Azalea</u> + many more.
- Tour Manager: Worked with all members of production to create, inspire, and delegate teams. Managed blockbuster events and tours. Created VIP experience packages for fans. Planned and executed multiple complex travel arrangements. Acts include: <u>Plain White T's</u>, <u>The Wild Feathers</u>, <u>Hanson</u> + many more.
- Audio Engineer: Responsible for all aspects of audio for concerts and events with capacity up to 80,000 people. High stress and high stakes trouble-shooting with complex audio systems. Maintained performance morale between management and artist. Highly autonomous. Acts include: Rage Against the Machine, Backstreet Boys, Usher, John Fogerty, Foo Fighters, Sara Bareilles + many more

Sound Image, San Diego, CA - Contract Global Account Manager: 2018-2021

- Coordinated and negotiated audio equipment for worldwide arena concert tours and events
- Closed an annual average of \$500k+ in sales and budget management

ECS Jets, Los Angeles, CA - Aviation Advisor/Sales: 2019-2020

- Sourced and maintained client relationships for a luxury private jet charter service
- Coordinated aircraft operators with international hubs on logistics and sourcing aircraft

Education

General Assembly- Remote - Software Engineering Immersive: 2021

Full Sail University- Orlando, FL - BA Entertainment Business and Recording Engineering: 2005-2007

Sparks Joy